Sync by vNaru
Kids, something you...
might not know about
your Uncle Marshall...
is that he's always been good at games.
I mean unbeatable.
Gin!
Yahtzee!
Poker!
You don't have to shout out 'poker'
when you win.
I know. It's just fun to say.
We all finally agreed,
Marshall should be
running our game nights,
instead of playing in them.
Which he took to mean,
'lnvent your own game.'
It's called 'Marshgammon.'
It combines all the best features
of all the best games,
Candyland, I Never, Pictionary.
- Backgammon, obviously.
- No.
Backgammon sucks.
I took the only good part of
'backgammon,' the 'gammon,'
and I left the rest of it in the trash
where it belongs.
I'm so excited Victoria's coming.
I'm gonna go get another round.
Okay. I wanna lay down
some ground rules for tonight, Barney.
I actually like Victoria a lot.
So, don't say anything...
Don't say anything.
And, guys, I haven't exactly told Victoria...
that I used to have a kind of thing for Robin,
- so if we could just avoid the...
- Well, well, well, how rich.
You make me promise to be on
my best behavior around your girlfriend,
yet you have been lying to her
since day one.
Excuse me.
Hi, Leg Warehouse?
Yeah, my friend Ted
needs something to stand on.
So, nothing for him to stand on?
Okay, thanks so much.
Ted, doesn't Victoria deserve to know
that you once had the hots for Robin?
I have half a mind
to tell the story of the re-return.
No,
I swore you to secrecy on that.
I am smelling dirt.
What is the story of the re-return?
Nothing. It's nothing.
And, speaking of digging up dirt,
can I count on you two
to behave around Victoria?
Us? What would we do?
Look, you guys have always been
like the parents that I still have,
and, in fact, moved here to get away from.
However, could we skip
the traditional interrogation...
of the new girlfriend tonight?
- Fine.
Thank you.
- I should go help Robin.
- Okay.
- Hey.
So, you gonna be okay
hanging out with Victoria tonight?
Oh, sure. She's great.
Oh, what? Because of the whole thing
where I said I liked Ted?
No. Victoria is great.
She's fun, she's free-spirited. She's great.
I said 'She's great' too many times,
didn't I?
You must really hate the bitch.
But if you roll an even number
while adjacent to the Peppermint Forest,
then you 'Marshall Out,'
and all your chips go into the pot.
And remember,
if you ever ask the question, 'What,'
then you gotta drink.
Got it?
- No idea what you're talking about.
Okay, okay. All right, no, no.
We'll just start. You guys will pick it up.
Newbie goes first.
- Roll.
- Okay.
Three! You got 'Autobiography.'
Now, that's where you have to answer
a personal question about your dating life,
truthfully, in order to move on.
- Marshall, come on.
- Hey. She's the one who rolled a three.
Victoria.
'Have you ever cheated
while in a relationship?'
Wow, good question.
- You don't have to answer that.
- It's okay.
Well, I was in a really crappy relationship
in college,
and I wound up kissing this guy
at a party one night...
and I felt terrible about it,
so I came clean and we broke up.
Victoria, that was an honest
and mature answer.
You may advance
to the Gumdrop Mountains.
So, Victoria,
did you ever re-return to this guy?
- What?
- You said what. You gotta drink.
Oh, Barney, by the way, I went to a party
in that new building on 82nd,
and the host said she knew you.
- What is her name? Sharon? Shannon?
- Shannon?
Shannon, Shannon.
No. Don't remember any Shannon.
Really? Well, 'cause she gave me
a videotape to give you.
Where's the tape?
I'll get it.
Cool. Okay. You know, whenever.
Okay, Robin. Your roll.
Five! Another 'Autobiography.'
For the player to your left which...
Victoria!
Of course.
Victoria.
'How many boyfriends did you have
before you started dating Ted?'
Wait, the card actually says Ted?
Okay. Well, boyfriends,
I guess I've only had two.
Prude-alert.
Well, that... That's serious boyfriends.
I've dated other guys in between.
Oh, slut-alert!
Oh, great, there it is.
Thanks, Lily, you're a peach.
Well, wow, look at that.
Robin landed on the Chocolate Swamp.
That's five chips for me.
Thank you. Finally,
somebody understands Marshgammon.
Barney, what was on that tape?
- Too bad you'll never find out.
- Damn it!
If only I'd given you a fake tape
and hidden the real tape in my purse.
Oh, wait. That's exactly what I did.
- What?
- Drink.
Yeah, you were acting so weird about it
I gave you Ted's graduation tape instead.
- So, should we pop it in?
- Give it to me.
- Hey, hey!
- Ted!
- Play it. Play it!
- Fine, fine.
I cannot believe...
Shannon! I love you.
I love you so much.
What about us
changing the world together?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
I know I haven't.
- Did you try his cell phone?
- Yeah, I left two messages.
I checked the cigar club,
the Lusty Leopard. He's off the grid.
Hey, guys. What up?
- Barney, where have you been?
- Yeah, we're really sorry about that.
Yeah, so sorry.
But seriously, what was up with the tape?
- No. Stay.
- Come on. Come on.
- Stay. Come on.
- I'm sorry. I don't wanna talk about it.
It was the most embarrassing
and humiliating thing...
that ever happened to me.
Well, we all have embarrassing stories.
Sometimes it's good to talk about it.
Oh, really?
Then why don't you tell us
your most humiliating moment, Marshall?
Show me how good it is.
All right.
I was stopping by Lily's
kindergarten class to say hi,
but they were all at recess.
I really had to pee,
so I went into the class's restroom.
It was a smaller target than I'm used to,
so I figured I should sit down.
What I didn't realize was
it was a shared bathroom.
I wish I'd pulled up my pants.
The kids still call him Funny Butt.
Okay. I'll tell you my story.
Believe it or not, I was not always
as awesome as I am today.
It was 1998.
I was just out of college,
and I was working at a coffeehouse
with my girlfriend.
My girlfriend, Shannon.
Thank you.
All right.
- I love your singing, Barney.
- And I love you, Shannon.
Joining the Peace Corps with you
is gonna be legendary.
I know. Only five short weeks,
till we're down in Nicaragua.
Hey, nonfat latte to go.
Mellow order, bro, mellow order.
Dude. That's your G-friend?
All right, high-five.
Sorry, I only give high-twos.
Whatevs. As long as you're nailing that.
Listen to you.'That'?
You know, women aren't objects.
They're human beings.
And FYI, Shannon and I have
decided to wait till we're married.
You can read about it in my zine.
Hey, Haircut, right here.
Open up your knowledge basket
'cause here it comes.
Forget all that touchy-feely crap.
You get money, you get laid.
End of discussion.
I feel sorry for you, man.
Peace out, hombre.
Suits.
Five weeks later, we were all set
to leave for the Peace Corps.
Only problem was...
she never showed up.
- She never showed?
- So what happened next?
You know what? This was a mistake.
Wait, what if somebody else
told their most humiliating story?
Oh, I know just how to decide who.
You brought the game to the bar?
We're not quitting
just 'cause Ted's so far ahead.
I was winning?
Fine. I'll go next.
I was doing a report on live TV
about a hansom cab driver.
- The slipping-in-horse-poop story?
- Yeah, we all know that one.
Okay, how about this?
I will tell you my most humiliating story.
Yeah, Victoria. Way to step up.
It involves a game of Truth or Dare,
a squeeze bottle
of marshmallow ice cream topping,
and the hot tub at my grandparents'
retirement community.
Kids, I tell you
a lot of inappropriate stories,
but there's no way in hell
I'm telling you this one.
Don't worry, though, it wasn't that great.
That is the greatest story ever!
- Oh, my God!
- Wow, wow, wow!
Victoria, I deem your offering worthy.
My saga continues.
I went back to the coffeehouse
to find Shannon.
- Barney!
- Sugar bear, where were you?
I'm sorry. My dad won't let me go.
But the Nicaraguans need us.
It's just he's still supporting me.
And, look,
he's coming by soon to talk about it,
but I think you should go on without me.
- Shannon, there is no...
- Barney.
It's your dream.
It's only two years. I know we can make it.
As I walked away,
I realized Shannon was an adult.
Her father couldn't control her life.
I had to go back and confront him.
She was in the middle
of a heated argument with her dad.
What?
Now we all gotta drink.
Oh, my God. What happened next?
- Oh, I don't know, guys.
- Okay, okay.
- Marshall's mom sent us cookies.
- Lily, no! No, Lily!
For the team, Marshall, for the team.
Hey, Mrs. Eriksen, it's Lily.
Thank you so much
for the delicious cookies.
Mayonnaise. Really?
Never would have guessed.
Yes, well I will definitely give Marshall
a kiss for you.
Okay, take care.
- Hi, baby.
- Oh, crap! My mom sent cookies?
Yeah. I wish we had a dog,
so they wouldn't go to waste.
Yeah.
So, we've got the whole place to ourselves.
- I'm thinking floor sex.
- Sounds reasonable.
Oh, floor's cold.
Grab that afghan your mom made.
The whole time?
The whole time.
Barney, that was really embarrassing
for both of us.
We just earned a huge chunk of story.
Right. So where was I?
Oh, yeah.
Shannon was sucking face with her dad.
How could... With your dad?
I mean, I know,
judge not lest ye be judged, but gross!
Barney, that's not my dad.
His name's Greg.
I've been seeing him for a few weeks.
I was hoping you'd just leave
and we could avoid all this.
We're breaking up?
But what about the Peace Corps?
Yeah, all this granola business,
it was just a phase.
Greg's older. He's successful.
He buys me all this cool stuff.
- But I love you.
- But he has a boat.
You should go to the Peace Corps.
And forget about me.
I didn't go.
That night, I recorded my video
and mailed it to Shannon.
I didn't see her until a week later.
There's sugar in the basket.
Shannon! Shannon, you came back!
I'm just picking up my last paycheck.
Did you... Did you get my tape?
Oh, she got the tape.
You? You... It was you?
Oh, man!
Oh, you poor thing.
The story's not over.
I did see Shannon one more time.
- When?
- Sorry. Sorry.
Oh, you've gotta tell us.
I don't know. I think I might need
one last story to get me through it.
Fine.
Oh, the Green Testicles story.
So, I was playing Ultimate Frisbee
in college,
and there was this barefoot dude
with a weirdly sharp toenail...
Oh, come on, Ted!
You know what story I wanna hear.
Everyone else here has manned-up tonight
and told the truth.
Why can't you?
You're right.
Victoria, I'm sorry I haven't
told you this yet, but a while back,
I was kind of into Robin.
In fact, on our first date,
I might've said, 'I love you.'
Understandably, she freaked out,
and I left,
but unfortunately,
the night did not end there.
We all ended up at the bar
with our cabdriver, Ranjit.
To one hell of a night!
And I drank.
A lot.
So, you guys think
I should have kissed her?
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna go kiss her. Right now.
Yes! Do it!
To the car.
Hello? Is someone out there?
You ralphed and ran?
I thought you were vomit-free since '93.
So, that was a lie?
You re-returned for me.
That's really sweet.
Though you kind of ruined
my customized Scherbatsky doormat.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
- Victoria, I know this must be...
- Yeah. It kind of is.
Wow, Ted, you were right.
You shouldn't have told that story.
But you did earn yourself
the right to the end of mine.
We fast-forward eight years into the future.
Wait, eight years. That's this year.
Marshall, not only is it this year,
it's tonight.
Hi.
- Barney?
- Hi, Shannon.
- What are you doing here?
- Just listen.
When you left me for that guy Greg,
it changed me.
Now, I'm this.
I know this is crazy, it's just,
you were once such a big part of my life,
and it just seemed insane
that you didn't know who I am now.
So, here I am.
And then she told me
about her life.
She and Greg dated for a while,
and then split up.
But here's the real kicker.
Shannon's a mom.
She has a little kid named Max.
That's crazy. That could've been my kid.
But instead, what do I have?
My whole life's some money in the bank,
some suits in my closet,
and a string of one-night stands.
Hey, come on.
I mean, just because her life went one way,
and yours went another,
doesn't make your life any worse.
My life rocks!
Money, suits and sex.
These are tears of joy.
I could be cooped up
in some tiny apartment,
changing some brat's poopy diapers,
but instead, I'm out in the world
being awesome 24/7, 365.
You let me dodge a bullet, Big Guy.
Plus, here's the mini-cherry,
on top of the regular cherry,
on top of the sundae of awesomeness
that is my life.
After Shannon and I talked, I nailed her.
- No.
- Yeah.
Sorry, don't buy it. You're making it up.
You're just trying to cover the fact
that you actually had a profound moment...
of doubt about yourself and...
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, Barney, oh.
Video's pretty good on this phone, huh?
Is your phone on?
Oh, no, it just takes a while
to power down.
Oh, gross. Just stop it.
Ladies, gentlemen, Ted.
This has been a wonderful evening.
I got great dirt on all you guys.
I got Ted to tell the re-return.
I finally nailed Shannon!
Told her I'd call her tomorrow.
Yeah, right.
And I rediscovered
just how awesomely awesome my life is.
Peace out, hombres.
I think Barney just won game night.
We spend so much effort
trying to keep parts of our lives hidden,
even from our closest friends...
that those rare times when we do open up,
it's amazing how minor those secrets
all end up seeming.
$100 says when you turn around...
Of course,
not every secret was told that night.
But that's getting ahead of the story.